https://azusastreetriders.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
loading...
Who we are
This is the official website of Azusa StreetRiders International, “the Apostolic Motorcycle Ministry of Jesus Christ.” Our web address is: https://azusastreetriders.com.
Our central purpose is to help lost souls receive a saving faith in the Lord Jesus Christ. We long to see you attain eternal life through faith in His name—saved from sin and suffering through repentance (turning away from sinful works), water baptism in the only saving name given under heaven & among men (Jesus; see Acts 4:12), and by being filled with the Holy Ghost (see Acts 2:1-4), which is “Christ in you, the hope of glory” (Colossians 1:27). As Oneness Pentecostal believers, we urge you to obey Acts 2:38, which declares, “Repent, and be baptized every one of you in the name of Jesus Christ for the remission of sins, and ye shall receive the gift of the Holy Ghost.”
This site’s primary functions are to disseminate the Gospel of Jesus Christ, to promote awareness of the Azusa StreetRiders International ministry, and (in part) to provide to each chapter and/or district and/or region of our ministry  an affordable web presence.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Chapter pages / websites
Whenever one of our local chapters posts updates of any kind or edits the content on their page or website that we provide, then obviously we collect all the data in such postings or edits. This is necessary for the function of the site according to part of its purpose.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
We never sell or give away your personally identifiable information to any other organization for any reason. We use the collected data within our own organization expressly in the direct fulfillment of the purposes of the website.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Any personally identifiable information you share with our site may be maintained in our records, and can be deleted upon your request, accompanied by a link to where your personally identifiable information is being displayed. The site staff can be reached by email at: support@azusastreetriders.com
Additional information
How we protect your data
We have installed a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) certificate that uses industrial strength encryption to protect logins and data transfers for both the parent domain name and all subdomains of the parent domain.
What data breach procedures we have in place
In the event of a data breach, we would notify the chapter(s) and/or district(s) and/or region(s) and/or leader(s) known to be affected, and work with them to mitigate the problem. However, whereas the chapters, districts, regions, and leaders are intentionally sharing their info publicly, there is very little in the way of private data that could be obtained in a breach. The most likely private data to be affected by a breach would be passwords, in which case changing the password would be the first step to take, and in fact a weak password will likely have been how the breach was incurred in the first place. We strongly recommend staff/volunteers use strong, complex passwords containing a mixture of upper and lower case letters, as well as numbers and special characters, avoiding easy to guess phrases and eschewing the use of whole words found in a common dictionary.
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
